NWLB Region II Office Files and Cases 5311
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- WBR #3 Region 2, Corrugated Box Industry 4/45, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 37)
- WBR #4 Region VIII, Telephone Industry, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 38)
- WBR #5 Region VIII, Natural Gas & Light and Power Ind. 6/45, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 39)
- WBR #6 Region X Switchboard Operators 4-45, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 40)
- WBR #7 Region X, Industrial Chemical Rates 4/45, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 41)
- WBR #8 Region X, Domestic Water Services 8/45, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 42)
- WBR #9 Region VIII, Warehousing Industry 6/45, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 43)
- WBR #10 Region IV, Electric Light & Power Industry 9/45, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 44)
- WBR #11 Region IV, Gas Mfg. & Distribution Industry 9/45, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 45)
- WBR #12 Region VII, Office & Clerical Occupations 9/45, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 46)
- WBR #13 Region VI, Foundry Rates 11/44, 1944 (Box 53, Folder 47)
- WBR #14 Region I, Electric & Gas Utilities 4/45, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 48)
- WBR #15 Region VII, Flour Milling Industry 9/45, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 49)
- WBR #16 Region VI, Tool & Die Makers 10/45, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 50)
- WBR #16 Region I, Ferrous Wire Drawing Rates 6/45, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 51)
- WBR #17 Region VII, Flour Milling Minima 11/44, 1944 (Box 53, Folder 52)
- WBR #18 Region V, Plant Protection Guards 8/45, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 53)
- WBR #19 Region IX, Maintenance Electricians A and B 10/45, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 54)
- WBR #20 Region VI, Metal Working Industry 5/45, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 55)
- WBR #22 Region VI, Radio- Radar Industry 10/44, 1944 (Box 53, Folder 56)
- WBR #23 Region 2, Ladies' Handbag & Pocketbook Ind. 6/45, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 57)
- WBR - Region VIII, Bakery Industry 9/44, 1944 (Box 53, Folder 58)
- WBR - Region VII, Various Industries and Areas 4/45, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 59)
- Summary of Significant Board Actions, No. 1 6/15/43, 1943 (Box 54, Folder 1)
- Summary of Significant Board Actions, No. 3 8/15/43, 1943 (Box 54, Folder 2)
- Summary of Significant Board Actions, No. 5 12/1/43, 1943 (Box 54, Folder 3)
- Summary of Significant Board Actions, No. 6 1/1/44, 1944 (Box 54, Folder 4)
- Summary of Significant Board Actions, No. 7 2/1/44, 1944 (Box 54, Folder 5)
- Summary of Significant Board Actions, No. 8 3/1/44, 1944 (Box 54, Folder 6)
- Appeals Supplement to Board Actions No. 1-8 3/1/44, 1944 (Box 54, Folder 7)
- Summary of Significant Board Actions, No. 9 3/1/44, 1944 (Box 54, Folder 8)
- Appeals Supplement to Board Actions No. 9 4/1/44, 1944 (Box 54, Folder 9)
- Summary of Significant Board Actions, No. 10 4/1/44, 1944 (Box 54, Folder 10)
- Appeals Supplement to Board Actions No. 10 5/1/44, 1944 (Box 54, Folder 11)
- Summary of Significant Board Actions, No. 11 5/1/44, 1944 (Box 54, Folder 12)
- Summary of Significant Board Actions, No. 12 6/1/44, 1944 (Box 54, Folder 13)
- Summary of Significant Board Actions, No. 13 7/1/44, 1944 (Box 54, Folder 14)
- Summary of Significant Board Actions, No. 14 8/1/44, 1944 (Box 54, Folder 15)
- Summary of Significant Board Actions, No. 15 9/1/44, 1944 (Box 54, Folder 16)
- Summary of Significant Board Actions, No. 16 3/1/45, 1945 (Box 54, Folder 17)
- Summary of Significant Board Actions, No. 17 4/1/45, 1945 (Box 54, Folder 18)
- Summary of Significant Board Actions, No. 18 9/1/45, 1945 (Box 54, Folder 19)
- National War Labor Board, 1945 (Box 55, Folder 1)
- NWLB 'TO: All Members of the Board', 1943 (Box 55, Folder 2)
- National War Labor Board Training Program, 1945 (Box 55, Folder 3)
- U.S. Labor Press Service Folder 1, 1944 (Box 55, Folder 4)
- U.S. Labor Press Service Folder 2, 1944 (Box 55, Folder 5)
- U.S. Labor Press Service, 1943 (Box 55, Folder 6)
- U.S. Labor Press Service, 1944 (Box 55, Folder 7)
- National War Labor Board Stabilization Division Summary of Significant Board Actions Number 9, 1944 (Box 55, Folder 8)
- Wage Stabilization General Orders and Interpretation, 1946 (Box 55, Folder 9)
- National War Labor Board Summary of Significant Board Actions, 1944 (Box 55, Folder 10)
- Index of National War Labor Board Directive Orders Dispute Cases by Issued Involved, 1943 (Box 55, Folder 11)